pushbullet.com 2013-08-21

# PushBullet - Easily push to your Android devices

#### What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter, or fill out a form.

When registering on our site, you may be asked to enter your e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

#### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience
  * To improve our website
  * To improve customer service
  * To send periodic emails

If you subscribe to our newsletter, your email address may be used to send you occasional company news and updates related to product or service information, etc. Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

#### How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

#### Do we use cookies?

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information)

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits.

#### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

#### Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

#### California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

#### Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

#### Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our Terms of Service section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at https://www.pushbullet.com/tos

#### Your Consent 

By using our site, you consent to our websites privacy policy.

#### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will update the Privacy Policy modification date below. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy from time to time to stay informed about how we are protecting the personally identifiable information we collect. If you continue to use our Service after we post an update to this Privacy Policy, this will indicate your acceptance of the update.

 **This policy was last modified on 01/31/2013**

#### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us at [privacy@pushbullet.com](mailto:privacy@pushbullet.com)
